HERE Communications Department Photographs 6199/005 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Display boards -- Photos mounted on foam display boards (Box 50, Folder 1)
  Miscellaneous photos of union members at work and at group gatherings